Russell D. White Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
Russell D. White Archives
1983-2002
IPAR.001229
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
1
The archives of Russell D. (Tim) White encompassing his career at Yale. These include maps and field notebooks.
White, Russell David
Biographical Sketch
Senior Collections Manager; Yale Peabody Museum
Description of the Material
Includes a geologic map of Kansas, topographic maps of Utah, field notes about a Cambrian carpoid locality in Utah, field notes from Hawaii and Utah (from a collecting trip with Llyod, Val and Glade Gunther, and Tom and Brian Whitely), and assorted slides.
Connecticut; Kansas; Utah; USA; Maps; Field notebooks; Yale Peabody Museum; Yale University
- Maps, Series I
  - Kansas., 001234
    - Geologic map. Geologic Map of Kansas, (1: 500000). State Geological Survey of Kansas: Geologic., 1964; 002194
  - Utah., 001233
    - Topographic map. Marjum Pass, UT 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1972; 002285
    - Topographic map. Notch Peak, UT 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1991; 002286
- Field Notes, Series II
  - 1983., 001235
    - Field notes. Field Notes of Cambrian Carpoid locality: House Range, Utah., 1983; 000190
  - 2000., 001236
    - Field notes. Field notes for photographs and collections from Hawaii (April-May, 2000) and Utah (May, 2000) collecting trip with the Lloyd, Val and Glade Gunther and Tom and Brian Whitely., 000730
- Miscellaneous, Series III
  Scope and Contents
  Miscellaneous Archives of Russell D. White.
  - Miscellaneous. Miscellaneous Archives mostly pertaining to the Yale Peabody Museum encompasing Russell D. White's career at Yale., 001238
    - Results of burst steam pipe on SW side of 5 Peabody, December 11, 1991. Mold growth discovered April 30, 1992. 35 mm color slides., 000541
    - 35 mm slides for volunteer orientation: The Good, The Bad and the Ugly! 35 mm slides. 1993?, 000542
  - Specimen Information., 001237
    - Type specimen catalogs with errata; Chelicerata, Trilobita, Gastropoda, 000819